Sutthirath Sean Vilaysane

Full Stack Developer | (206) 773 - 8006

seanvilaysane.com | seanvilaysane@gmail.com | github.com/sutthirath | linkedin.com/in/seanvilaysane

Skills & Expertise

Front-End Development | React, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Ejs, Mapbox, Bootstrap, Material UI

Back-End Development | Node, Express, Python, Django, MongoDB, Postgresql

Developer Tools | Visual Studio Code, Atom, Github, Chrome Dev Tools, Bash, Adobe XD, Slack

Projects

Yocal | Nov 2018

Yocal is a full-stack application built with the Mongo, Express, React, and Node stack. This mobile app is for fearless travellers who love to explore new lands. A seamless user experience for searching local places using the foursquare API. Travellers can chat real-time with local experts to get instant advise.

Seattle Transit | Nov 2018

Seattle Transit is a full-stack application built with the collaboration of Henry Hong and Christopher Tack. This application is developed with Node.js, Express.js and Ejs. My role in the project was more frontend. I took charge of the user interface and experience as well as the mapbox api integration.

Bug Invaders | Sep 2018

Bug Invaders is a web application game. Developed with vanilla Javascript to hone my DOM manipulation skills. This is a basic defender and wave type game. Utilizing a setInterval game loop for the gameplay to create new enemies on the DOM and increase the speed.

Professional Experience

Office Administrator | Columbia Hospitality | Seattle, WA | Mar 2018 - Aug 2018

Run daily reports and update meeting schedules. Liaison between client and meet planner. Prep meeting rooms and ensure client's needs are meet. In charge of creating and designing signage.

Lead Front Office Agent | Hotel FIVE | Seattle, WA | Mar 2016 - Jan 2018

Performed as the Manager's personal "tech guy" by assisting with all tech inquiries such as networking connectivity, OPERA troubleshooting, and other general issues. Mentored new agents and ensure the success of their accomplishments. Developed new or improve operational procedures and policies to better satisfy company regulations while giving the absolute premium experience for our guests. Maintained the safety of all personnel on the property by preventative quality checks and enforced surveillance.

Front Office Agent | Hyatt Regency Orlando International Airport | Orlando, FL | May 2015 - Oct 2015

Responsible for checking guests in and out of the property with expertise. Delivered authentic hospitality and guest service by exceeding customer satisfaction. Utilized employee empowerment by investigating concerns and resolving issues. Assembled a plethora of knowledge of the property and area that can rival a concierge. Increased the department revenue by up-selling rooms with creative suggestion.

Education

Web Development Immersive | General Assembly | Seattle, WA | Graduated Dec 2018

B.S. Hospitality Management | University of Central Florida | Orlando, FL | Graduated Dec 2015